Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Cross Dressers Book Club
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Cross dressers book club
1980-1982
Bailey 16
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
31 v.; 18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, including forced feminization.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, including forced feminization.
All individual titles paperbound.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Cross Dressers Book Club
  - She-male nurse, c1980; CD_1_ (Box 1-32)
  - Her panty slave, c1980; CD_2_ (Box 1-32)
  - Housemaid husband, c1980; CD_3_ (Box 1-32)
  - Cross dressed banker, c1980; CD_4_ (Box 1-32)
  - She-male slave, c1980; CD_5_ (Box 1-32)
  - Forced to be a woman, c1980; CD_6_ (Box 1-32)
  - Her night on top, c1980; CD_7_ (Box 1-32)
    Scope and Contents
    Stamp on bottom edge: SBN [?]
  - Dressed in mama's panties, c1980; CD_8_ (Box 1-32)
  - Transvestite tease, c1980; CD_9_ (Box 1-32)
  - "T.p. title:Forced into sister's heels Cover title: Forced into high heels", c1980; CD_10_ (Box 1-32)
    Price label on front cover: 1.50, 4/5
  - She male husband, c1980; CD_11_ (Box 1-32)
    Stamp on top edge: MBN
  - Madame's TV slave, c1980; CD_12_ (Box 1-32)
    Price label on front cover: $2 ea., 3 for $5
  - The banker's secret, c1981; CD_13_ (Box 1-32)
  - The newlywed's experiment, c1981; CD_14_ (Box 1-32)
    Stamp on bottom edge: SBN
  - Cross-dressing daddy, c1981; CD_15_ (Box 1-32)
  - Studs in pink panties, c1981; CD_16_ (Box 1-32)
  - Cross dressed submissive, c1981; CD_17_ (Box 1-32)
  - Trained by his mama, c1981; CD_18_ (Box 1-32)
    Price label on front cover: $1.50
  - His secret wardrobe, c1981; CD_19_ (Box 1-32)
    "Price label on front cover: $1.50 each, 4 for $5.00 Stamp on top edge: Jun. 8"
  - The man in silk, c1981; CD_20_ (Box 1-32)
    Price label on front cover: $1.50 each, 4 for $5.00
  - Harlot houseboy, c1981; CD_21_ (Box 1-32)
    "Price label on front cover: 1.50, 4/5 Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist."
  - Petticoat discipline, c1981; CD_22_ (Box 1-32)
    "Price label on front cover: $1.50 Stamp on top edge: MBI"
  - She-male for sale, c1981; CD_23_ (Box 1-32)
  - "T.p. title: She cross-dressed her boss Cover title:Cross-dressed executive", c1981; CD_24_ (Box 1-32)
  - Momma's girls, c1981; CD_25_ (Box 1-32)
  - Male maid, c1981; CD_26_ (Box 1-32)
  - Degraded husband, c1981; CD_27_ (Box 1-32)
  - Satin slaves, c1982; CD_29_ (Box 1-32)
  - TV training, c1982; CD_30_ (Box 1-32)
  - Momma's boy-girl, c1982; CD_31_ (Box 1-32)
  - Shamed she-male, c1982; CD_32_ (Box 1-32)